Register of the Edward Geary Lansdale papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Sound Recordings, 1951-1975
  - Senior Liaison Office staff and friends, 1965-1975
    - Tape 6, Vietnam, 1965 November 25
      - 14. "Winter for the Fighting Men," Pham Duy (Vietnamese)
      - 15. "Carrying Paddy to the Soldiers," Pham Duy (Vietnamese)
    - Tape 7, Vietnam, 1965 December 18
      Use copy reference number: 80116_a_0012360
      This tape is a recording of an "SLO pre-curfew party" in Saigon at 194 Cong Ly. Radio Hanoi had just announced the beginning of "hate Americans" week, and during the same broadcast had threatened to assassinate General Lansdale. The residents of Cong Ly (with their neighbors' permission) gave a loud street party to invite an attack, for which they were prepared.
      Several people sing and entertain. One soloist, Sgt. Roger Hopkins, was not known at Cong Ly but wandered into the party after hearing the music as he passed by in his car. Pham Duy announces his songs in English and Vietnamese, and performs them with his group, The Villagers. The recording of this party is continued on tapes 8-10.
      - 1. Entry song, Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
      - 2. "Fisherman's Song," Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
      - 3. North Vietnamese folk song, Miss Gian (Vietnamese)
      - 4. Phan Rang folk song, Miss Gian (Vietnamese)
      - 5. Jam session (instrumental, zither and guitars)
      - 6. "The Fox," Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
      - 7. "Blow Ye Winds," Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
      - 8. "Town Hall Light," Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
      - 9. "Travelin' on," Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
      - 10. "John Hardie," Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
      - 11. "Greensleeves," Pham Duy and Bernie Yoh
      - 12. Villagers' theme, Bernie Yoh and Pham Duy
      - 13. "Hunter's ROTC Is the Name," Johnny San Juan and Hunter's veterans (English)
      - 14. "Hunter's March," Johnny San Juan and Hunter's veterans (English)
      - 15. "Guerrilla Kundiman," Johnny San Juan and Hunter's veterans (English)
      - 16. "Mother Vietnam Tone Poem," Chieu Hoi Singers, Chi Lin, Chu Mai, Lieu Lung (Vietnamese)
      - 17. "Vietnam, Vietnam," Chieu Hoi Singers (Vietnamese)
    - Tape 8, Vietnam, 1965 December 18
      This is a continuation of tape 7, the "SLO pre-curfew party." The "Embassy Boys Choir" was a pseudonym for certain CIA personnel who gathered in a little bar (the "Cosmos") behind the American Embassy after work each day. Their songs were parodies born between drinks.
      - 18. "Summertime," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 19. "Twelve Days of Christmas," Embassy Boys Choir (English)
      - 20. "Silent Night," The Villagers (Vietnamese)
      - 21. "Rose, Rose I Love You" (instrumental)
      - 22. "China Nights" (instrumental)
      - 23. "You're My Gambling Life" (instrumental)
      - 24. "Roving Gambler," Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
      - 25. "Streets of Loredo," Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
      - 26. "Frere Jacques" (instrumental)
      - 27. "This Train," Sgt. Roger Hopkins, Pham Duy, Bernie Yoh (English)
      - 28. Vietnamese zither music
      - 29. "Rain on the Leaves," Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
      - 30. "Sing With Me," Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
      - 31. "Silent Night," Ambassador Lodge and group (English)
      - 32. "The Wounded Soldier," Pham Duy and Art Juliano (Vietnamese and English)
      - 33. "Rain on the Leaves," Pham Duy and Art Juliano (Vietnamese and English)
      - 34. "Sing With Me," Pham Duy and Art Juliano (Vietnamese and English)
      - 35. "CVT Marching Song," CVT members (English)
    - Tape 9, Vietnam, 1965 December 18
      This is a continuation from tapes 7 and 8.
      - 36. "Sunset," Chi Lin (Vietnamese)
      - 37. "Vietnamese Love Song," Chieu Hoi Singers (Vietnamese)
      - 38. "Twelve Days of Christmas," Embassy Boys Choir (English)
      - 39. "Silent Night," Embassy Boys Choir (English)
      - 40. "Escape of John Webb," Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
      - 41. "Appalachian Song," Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
      - 42. "Old King Cole," Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
      - 43. "Last Summer," Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
      - 44. "Take This Hammer," Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
      - 45. "On Top of Old Smokey," Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
      - 46. "You Are My Sunshine," Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
      - 47. "White Christmas," Filipina woman and Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
      - 48. "Tinikling," Filipinos (instrumental)
      - 49. "Alcamphor Dance," Filipinos (instrumental)
      - 50. "Tinikling," group (instrumental)
    - Tape 10, Vietnam, 1965 December 18
      This is a continuation of tapes 7-9, and the last of this series.
      - 51. Vietnamese song, Pham Duy (Vietnamese)
      - 52. Viet Minh youth songs, Pham Duy (Vietnamese)
      - 53. "Riverboat," Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
      - 54. "Hawaiian War Dance," Bernie Yoh, Pham Duy, Sgt. Roger Hopkins, and others
      - 55. "Tahitian Rhythm," Dan Ellsberg
      - 56. "Twist," Sgt. Roger Hopkins
      - 57. "Darling Corey," Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
      - 58. "Indian Dance," Sgt. Roger Hopkins
      - 59. "Hillbilly," Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
      - 60. Guitars, Sgt. Roger Hopkins and Bernie Yoh
      - 61. "SLO Spell It Song," group (English)
      - 62. "SLO, Team Team Team," Sgt. Roger Hopkins and Sam Karrick
    - Tape 11, Vietnam, 1966 July 21
      Use copy reference number: 80116_a_0012373
      This tape was recorded at 194 Cong Ly. Pham Duy, Steve Addis, and Sam Wilson and his wife, Brenda, all sing.
      - 1. "Rain on the Leaves," Steve Addis and Pham Duy (Vietnamese and English)
      - 2. "Rambling Boy," Steve Addis and group with Pham Duy on zither (English)
      - 3. "Clementine," Steve Addis and Pham Duy (Vietnamese and English)
      - 4. "Harvest Moon," Sam and Brenda Wilson (English)
      - 5. "From Out of Nowhere," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 6. "Dirty Old Town," Steve Addis (English)
        The following were recorded at an earlier time, and spliced on to this tape:
      - 7. "Rain on the Leaves," Mitch Miller and chorus (English)
      - 8. "Revolutionary Development Cadre Song," Pham Duy (Vietnamese)
      - 9. "We Shall Overcome," Pham Duy (Vietnamese); Pham Duy and students (Vietnamese)
      - 10. "Rain on the Leaves," Sgt. Roger Hopkins (English)
    - Tape 12, Vietnam, 1966 July 29
      Use copy reference number: 80116_a_0012372
      This tape was recorded at 194 Cong Ly. It is entitiled "Songs by Pham Duy, Steve Addis, and Captain Hershel Gober." It goes with tape 13, which is a continuation.
      - 1. "Ballad of the Green Beret," Pham Duy (Vietnamese) and Hershel Gober (English)
      - 2. "Tropic Rain," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 3. "Proud American," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 4. Vietnamese song, Pham Duy and Steve Addis (Vietnamese)
      - 5. "The Wounded Soldier," Steve Addis and Pham Duy (Vietnamese and English)
      - 6. "Rain on the Leaves," Steve Addis and Pham Duy (Vietnamese and English)
      - 7. "Dirty Old Town," Steve Addis and Hershel Gober (English)
      - 8. "500 Miles," Steve Addis and Hershel Gober (English)
      - 9. "Clementine," Steve Addis, Pham Duy, and Hershel Gober (Vietnamese and English)
      - 10. "I'm Just a Dog-Faced Soldier," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 11. "Big Sam," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 12. "Bulgar Wheat," Hershel Gober (English)
        The following was recorded at an earlier time, and spliced on to this tape. It is dedicated by Pham Duy to General Lansdale.
      - 13. "Fisherman's Song," Pham Duy and friends (Vietnamese)
    - Tape 13, Vietnam, 1966 July 29 (Box 86)
      This is a continuation from tape 12.
      - 1. "Look Over My Shoulder," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 2. "Portrait of a Man," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 3. "Saigon Warrior," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 4. "Advisory Team 1004," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 5. "The Forgotten Man," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 6. "Here Am I," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 7. "I Need You So," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 8. "Tropic Rain," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 9. "Proud American," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 10. "Bulgar Wheat," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 11. "Dirty Old Town," Hershel Gober and Steve Addis (English)
      - 12. "500 Miles," Hershel Gober and Steve Addis (English)
      - 13. "Clementine," Hershel Gober, Pham Duy and Steve Addis (Vietnamese and English)
    - Tape 14, Vietnam, 1966 September 4
      Use copy reference number: 80116_a_0012391
      This tape contains Vietnamese songs and one Korean song recorded at 194 Cong Ly. Lansdale invited Pham Duy, along with three Vietnamese women (from Pham Duy's band, The Villagers), to record Vietnamese folk songs. They are joined by Steve Addis. Colonel Sam Wilson and Brenda Wilson also perform a few numbers. This recording session is continued on tapes 15 and 16.
      - 1. "Hat Hoi Trang Ram" (folksong from the North), Pham Duy, The Villagers, and Steve Addis (Vietnamese)
      - 2. "Planting Rice" (folksong from the Philippines), Pham Duy, The Villagers, and Steve Addis (Vietnamese)
      - 3. "Arrirang," Vietnamese woman (Korean)
      - 4. "Rain on the Leaves," Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
      - 5. "It's the Last Thing on My Mind," Steve Addis and Vietnamese woman (English)
      - 6. "One, Two Buckle My Shoe," Steve Addis (English)
      - 7. "It's Many a Mile," Steve Addis (English)
      - 8. "Red River Valley," Steve Addis and Vietnamese woman (English and Vietnamese)
      - 9. "Sheik of Araby," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 10. "Lazy River," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 11. "Jack of Diamonds," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 12. "Old Bill Bailey," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 13. "Cuddle Up a Little Closer," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 14. "Let Me Call You Sweetheart," Sam Wilson (English)
    - Tape 15, Vietnam, 1966 September 4
      This is a continuation of the recording session begun on tape 14. Now Jim Bullington joins the group. Steve Addis, Pham Duy, and the three women sing again.
      - 1. "Brave Boys," Jim Bullington (English)
      - 2. "Tai Shau--If the VC Don't Get Me Tomorrow," Jim Bullington (English)
      - 3. "Brave Young Co Van My," Jim Bullington (English)
      - 4. "Way Down Upon the Perfume River," Jim Bullington (English)
      - 5. "Silent Night" (instrumental - zither)
      - 6. "Blues on My Ceiling," Steve Addis (English)
      - 7. "Suc Mai My Bun," Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
      - 8. "Vietnam, Vietnam," Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
      - 9. Vietnamese song (instrumental - zither)
    - Tape 16, Vietnam, 1966 September 4
      This is the third tape of the recording session begun on tape 14. Pham Duy talks for a while, and then sings Hershel Gober's song, "Picture of a Man," with the three Vietnamese women.
      - 1. "Picture of a Man," Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
      - 2. "Theme--Cast of Merrill's Marauders," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 3. Wilson on Saigon (instrumental)
      - 4. "I'm Funny That Way," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 5. "Clementine," Pham Duy and The Villagers, Steve Addis, and Brenda Wilson (English and Vietnamese)
      - 6. "Rain on the Leaves," Pham Duy and Steve Addis (Vietnamese and English)
      - 7. "The Wounded Soldier" Pham Duy and Steve Addis (Vietnamese and English)
      - 8. "Here's to You My Rambling Boy," Steve Addis and Brenda Wilson (English)
    - Tape 17, Vietnam, 1966 September 21
      Use copy reference number: 80116_a_0012396
      This is a recording of an impromptu "happy hour" at 194 Cong Ly. It took place just after the elections for a Constituent Assembly in Vietnam, on which General Thang (with the help of the SLO) had worked to keep the process free and honest. Prime Minister Ky phoned General Lansdale after the returns started to come in, announcing that people felt the elections had been honest, and suggesting a celebration. General Lansdale invited Ky's staff and the SLO staff, as well as Ambassador Lodge, to his place.
      Pham Duy speaks in Vietnamese before each of his songs. Hershel Gober, and Pham Duy's group, The Villagers, also sing. This is the first of four tapes (17-20) recorded on this date.
      - 1. "Advisory Team 54," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 2. "Hat Hoi Trang Ram," Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
      - 3. "Hat Do Due" (love song from the North), Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
      - 4. "Ly Chim Khu Yen" (song of the nightingale), Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
      - 5. "Clementine," Pham Duy, Steve Addis, and The Villagers (Vietnamese and English)
      - 6. "Planting Rice," Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese and Tagalog)
      - 7. "Arirang" (Korean love song) Pham Duy and The Villagers (Korean)
      - 8. "Picture of a Man," Pham Duy, Hershel Gober, and The Villagers (Vietnamese and English)
      - 9. "Birth of a Nation," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 10. "Bulgar Wheat," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 11. "Red River Valley," Sam Wilson and The Villagers (Vietnamese and English)
      - 12. "Suc May Ma Buon," Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
      - 13. "Ngheo Ma Khong Ham," Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
      - 14. "Nhac Tuoi Xanh" (youth song), Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
    - Tape 18, Vietnam, 1966 September 21
      This is a continuation from tape 17. Ambassador Lodge sings on this tape and Prime Minister Ky comments.
      - 15. "Dirty Old Town," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 16. "We Got Us Some Chickens," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 17. "Look Over My Shoulder," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 18. "Ballad of the Green Beret," Pham Duy and Hershel Gober (Vietnamese and English)
      - 19. "I'm Just a Dog-Faced Soldier," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 20. "Saigon Warrior," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 21. "Tropic Rain," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 22. "Proud American," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 23. "I Need You So," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 24. "A Personal Friend of Mine," Ambassador Lodge (English, French, German, and "Vietnamese")
        At this point, the Prime Minister comments that "only the Viet Cong can understand Ambassador Lodge's Vietnamese."
      - 25. "Mona Lisa," Lt. Nguyen Kin Dinh
    - Tape 19, Vietnam, 1966 September 21
      This is a continuation from tapes 17 and 18. Ambassador Lodge and Prime Minister Ky both sing, as does Colonel Sam Wilson.
      - 26. "Gui Gio Cho May Ngan Bay," Lt. Nguyen Kin Dinh (Vietnamese)
      - 27. "Tien Em," Prime Minister Ky and Pham Duy (Vietnamese)
      - 28. "Toi Co Nguoi Em Nho," Prime Minister Ky and Pham Duy (Vietnamese)
      - 29. "Plaisir d'Amour," Ambassador Lodge and The Villagers (English)
      - 30. "Let Me Call You Sweetheart," Ambassador Lodge and The Villagers (English)
      - 31. "Up a Lazy River," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 32. "Bill Bailey," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 33. "Jack of Diamonds," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 34. "Street of Dreams," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 35. "Truckin' on Down," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 36. "Is You Is or Is You Ain't My Baby," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 37. "Sheik of Araby," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 38. "The Man I Love," Ambassador Lodge (English)
      - 39. "Indian Summer," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 40. "Talk of the Town," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 41. "Thuong Tinh Ca," Prime Minister Ky and Pham Duy (Vietnamese)
      - 42. "Souvenir," Pham Duy (Vietnamese)
      - 43. "Vietnam, Vietnam," Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
    - Tape 20, Vietnam, 1966 September 21
      This is a continuation of tapes 17-19. It is entitled "after party," and is the last of this series. Prime Minister Ky left the party before this tape was recorded.
      - 44. "Birth of a Nation," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 45. "Saigon Warrior," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 46. "I Got a Letter (I'm a Star)," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 47. "He Wears a Jungle Uniform," Jim Bullington (English)
      - 48. "Dang Me," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 49. "Chug-A-Lug," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 50. Song to the tune of "Did He Ever Return," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 51. "Walbash Cannonball," group (English)
      - 52. "In the Heart of Tennessee," group (English)
      - 53. "In the Evening," group (English)
      - 54. "You Are My Sunshine," group (English)
      - 55. "Beautiful Brown Eyes," group (English)
      - 56. "Roll Me Over in the Clover," group (English)
      - 57. "She's Funny That Way," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 58. "You Came to Me from Out of Nowhere," Sam Wilson (English)
      - 59. Guitar music, Sam Wilson (instrumental)
      - 60. "Oh Cherchonia," Sam Wilson (English)
    - Tape 21, Vietnam, 1966 September 30
      Use copy reference number: 80116_a_0000684
      This tape is a recording of "Captain Hershel Gober and the Black Patches." The recording was made at 194 Cong Ly. This is the first in a series of three tapes: 21-23. The tape begins with instrumental music, then Captain Hershel Gober and his band are introduced. Gober thanks the "ladies and gentlemen, Mr. Ambassador, our gracious host, General Lansdale," and begins to perform a show which he says will be played for soldiers in the field.
      After one number, General Lansdale breaks in to explain who the musicians are and what they're doing. He talks about Hershel Gober, who Lansdale has known since they served together in Germany. Lansdale suggested to General Westmoreland that Gober assemble a band, which would go out and entertain servicemen at far-away outposts that the USO might not reach. Four other musicians were pulled from "all over Vietnam" to assemble the band, which plays on the remainder of this tape.
      There is a large audience, evidently including Ambassador Lodge.
      - 1. Instrumental
      - 2. "Goodbye Travis Air Force Base," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 3. "Blue Suede Shoes," Hershel Gober and the Black Patches, Sgt. Marvin Elrod (English)
      - 4. "Buckaroo," Hershel Gober and the Black Patches, Sgt. Toppings (English)
      - 5. "I Left My Heart in San Francisco," Hershel Gober and the Black Patches, Dexter Adler (English)
      - 6. "Bye Bye Happiness," Hershel Gober and the Black Patches (English)
      - 7. "Comanche," Hershel Gober and the Black Patches, Jimmy Tobias (English)
      - 8. "Big Bad Bruce," Hershel Gober and the Black Patches, Jimmy Tobias (English)
      - 9. "Six Clicks," Hershel Gober and the Black Patches (English)
      - 10. "Saigon Warrior," Hershel Gober and the Black Patches (English)
    - Tape 22, Vietnam, 1966 September 30
      This is a continuation from tape 21.
      - 11. "Tennessee Waltz," Hershel Gober and the Black Patches, Sgts. Elrod and Toppings (English)
      - 12. Instrumental
      - 13. "Bill Bailey," Hershel Gober and the Black Patches, Dexter Alder (English)
      - 14. "Black Patches," Hershel Gober and the Black Patches, Dexter Alder (English)
      - 15. "Kansas City," Hershel Gober and the Black Patches, Dexter Alder (English)
      - 16. "Mrs. Miller," Hershel Gober and the Black Patches, Jimmy Tobias (English)
      - 17. Instrumental
      - 18. "Mountain Dew," Hershel Gober and the Black Patches (English)
      - 19. "Look Over My Shoulder," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 20. "Proud American," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 21. "Here Am I," Hershel Gober (English)
    - Tape 23, Vietnam, 1966 September 30
      Use copy reference number: 80116_a_0000683
      This is a continuation from tapes 21 and 22. Hershel Gober sings alone on this tape.
      - 22. "Tropic Rain," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 23. "Advisory Team 54," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 24. "I'm Just a Dog-Faced Soldier" (dedicated to General Lansdale), Hershel Gober (English)
      - 25. "Bulgar Wheat," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 26. "We Had Us Some Chickens," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 27. "Black Patches," Hershel Gober and the Black Patches (instrumental)
      - 28. "Dirty Old Town," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 29. "You Are My Sunshine," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 30. "Tom Dooley," Hershel Gober (English)
    - Tape 24, Vietnam, 1966 December 11
      Use copy reference number: 2000c120_a_0012408
      This tape is labelled, "Pre-Tet: Christmas, 194 Cong Ly." It is the first in a series of three tapes: 24, 25, and 26. It is evidently a recording of a large gathering, including Hershel Gober, Sam Wilson, Pham Duy, and Pham Duy's group, The Villagers. All sing.
      - 1. "The Battle of Long Khanh (6th Royal Australian Regiment)," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 2. "Dirty Old Town," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 3. "Answer to the Green Beret," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 4. "Planting Rice," Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese and Tagalog)
      - 5. "Picture of a Man," Pham Duy and Hershel Gober (Vietnamese and English)
      - 6. "The Wounded Soldier," Pham Duy (Vietnamese)
      - 7. "Suc May Ma Boun," Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
        After this song, General Lansdale presents a certificate of appreciation to Hershel Gober. Gober then gives a speech, and General Lansdale reads the citation.
    - Tape 25, Vietnam, 1966 December 11
      Use copy reference number: 80116_a_0012407
      This is a continuation from tape 24.
      - 1. "Six Clicks," Hershel Gober (English)
        After this song, Hank Miller "promotes" General Lansdale to the "Office of Regional Deputy Archbastard" in the "Order of the Old Bastard."
      - 2. "Deep in the Heart of Tennessee," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 3. "Michael, Row the Boat Ashore," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 4. "Advisory Team 54," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 5. "Cadre Song," Pham Duy (Vietnamese)
      - 6. "To Sing Often Is Better than to Sing with a Good Voice," Pham Duy (Vietnamese)
        At this point someone announces that Prime Minister Ky is going to sing.
      - 7. Vietnamese song, Prime Minister Ky (Vietnamese)
      - 8. "Silent Night," Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
      - 9. "Jingle Bells," Hershel Gober and Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese and English)
      - 10. "Vietnam, Vietnam," Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
      - 11. "Rain on the Leaves," Pham Duy, Hershel Gober, and group (English)
      - 12. "Oh Susannah," group (English and Vietnamese)
      - 13. "Clementine," Pham Duy and group (English and Vietnamese)
      - 14. "Hat Hoi Trang Ram," Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
      - 15. Vietnamese song, Pham Duy and The Villagers (Vietnamese)
      - 16. "Big Sam," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 17. "Dirty Old Town," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 18. "You Are My Sunshine," group (English)
      - 19. "Let the Rest of the World Go By," Hershel Gober and group (English)
    - Tape 26, Vietnam, 1966 December 11
      This is a continuation from tapes 24 and 25.
      - 1. "My Blue Heaven," group (English)
      - 2. "Darktown Strutters' Ball" (instrumental)
      - 3. "Silver Dollar," group (English)
      - 4. "Red River Valley," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 5. "Anybody Seen My Gal," group (English)
      - 6. "Love Letters in the Sand," group (English)
      - 7. "My Pretty Freulein," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 8. "Auld Lang Syne," Hershel Gober (English)
    - Tape 27, Vietnam, 1966 December 11
      Use copy reference number: 80116_a_0012417
      This is a recording of a "Salute to Captain Hershel Gober by General Westmorland." General Westmorland speaks, then Hershel Gober sings excerpts of his songs.
      - 1. "Goodbye Travis Air Force Base," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 2. "The Forgotten Man," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 3. "Picture Of A Man," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 4. "Birth Of A Nation," Hershel Gober (English)
      - 5. "Saigon Warrior," Hershel Gober (English)